Guide to the Stan Healy Photographs and Papers 1890s-1990s (bulk 1940s-1970s)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Accession 1990-016 Photographs, circa 1890s-1970s; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (2,700 images)
  - Swan Valley Search and Rescue truck on Higgins Avenue near the Atlantic Hotel in the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0751A)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0751B)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0752)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0753)
  - Missoula fire truck turning onto Higgins Avenue for the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montan, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0754A)
  - Missoula fire truck turning onto Higgins Avenue by the Park Hotel and Cafe for the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0754B)
  - A small Missoula fire truck turning onto Higgins Avenue by the Park Cafe for the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0755A)
  - A water truck turning onto Higgins Avenue by the Park Hotel and Cafe for the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0755B)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0756)
  - Higgins Avenue, Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0757)
  - Missoula County Sheriff's Association Search and Rescue truck on Higgins Avenue near the Atlantic Hotel in the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0758A)
  - Montana 4x4 patrol truck pulling a radio communications trailer on Higgins Avenue near the Atlantic Hotel in the Fire Prevention parade, Missoula, Montana, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0758B)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0759)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0760)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0761)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0762)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0763)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0764)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0765)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0766)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0767)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 10, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0768)
  - Phillips 66 fire, battled by firemen and engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0769)
  - Pine Street, laying gravel in new fire station parking lot, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0770)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0771)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0772)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0773)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0774)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0775)
  - Pine Street, construction begins on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0776)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station parking lot, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0777)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, May 13, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0778)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, March 8, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0779)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, March 8, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0780)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, March 8, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0781)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0782)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0783)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0784)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0785)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0786)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0787)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0788)
  - Firemen, laying out hose to dry and roll, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0789)
  - Fire at Larson Body and Fender Works, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0790)
  - Fire at Larson Body and Fender Works, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0791)
  - Fire at Larson Body and Fender Works, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0792)
  - Fire at Larson Body and Fender Works, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0793)
  - Fire, Higgins Avenue, Ogg's Shoes and Save On Drug, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0794)
  - Fire, Higgins Avenue, Ogg's Shoes and Save On Drug, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0795)
  - Fire, Higgins Avenue, Ogg's Shoes and Save On Drug, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0796)
  - Fire, Higgins Avenue, Ogg's Shoes and Save On Drug, Missoula, Montana, July 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0797)
  - Broadway Avenue, looking at a fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0798)
  - Pine Street, children tour the new fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0799)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, February 24, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0800)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, February 24, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0801)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, February 24, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0802)
  - Fire engines at the scene of the Phillips 66 fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0803)
  - Fire engine being pushed out of the station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0804)
  - Army personnel posing with their fire engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0805A)
  - Large culvert being installed in the ground, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0805B)
  - Army personnel posing with their fire engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0806)
  - Army personnel posing with their fire engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0807)
  - Army personnel posing with their fire engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0808)
  - Army personnel posing with their fire engines, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0809)
  - Pine Street, new fire station near Louie's Garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0810)
  - Pine Street, fire staff posing at fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0811)
  - Pine Street, fire staff posing at fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0812)
  - Pine Street, fire staff posing at fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0813)
  - Pine Street, inside of new fire station, Missoula, Montana, January 1956 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0814)
  - Pine Street, new fire station near Louie's Garage, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0815)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station drive, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0816)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station drive, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0817)
  - Pine Street, old fire department staff posing, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0818)
  - Missoula fire wagon on Pine Street, St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church, Missoula, Montana, 1892 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0819)
  - Missoula fire wagon on Pine Street, St. Francis Xavier Catholic Church, Missoula, Montana, 1892 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0820)
  - Missoula fire engine #6, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0821)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, circa 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0822)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, circa 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0823)
  - Missoula fire chief's car, Missoula, Montana, 1911 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0824)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, circa 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0825)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, 1899 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0826)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew near Nagle Livery, Missoula, Montana, 1918 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0827)
  - Missoula fire engine and staff at Missoula Garage, Missoula, Montana, 1918 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0828)
  - Missoula fire staff, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0829)
  - Missoula fire engine at the Nagle Livery Stable, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0830)
  - Missoula fire wagon and horses, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0831)
  - Missoula fire engine and staff, Missoula, Montana, circa 1911 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0832)
  - Missoula fire engine and staff at Missoula Garage, Missoula, Montana, 1918 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0833)
  - Missoula fire chief's car, Missoula, Montana, 1911 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0834)
  - Missoula fire staff in front of engines, Missoula, Montana, 1918 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0835)
  - Missoula fire staff in uniform, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0836)
  - Missoula fire department champion wet test running team, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0837)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0838)
  - Missoula fire wagon, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0839)
  - Missoula fire wagon and crew, Missoula, Montana, 1891 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0840)
  - Missoula fire engine in action at a stop light, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0841)
  - Unidentified fireman, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0842)
  - A view of some fire engines parked in the station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0843)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station drive, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0844)
  - Missoula fire department crew, Missoula, Montana, 1898 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0845)
  - People touring a fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0846)
  - Fire engines parked in their station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0847)
  - People touring a fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0848)
  - Firemen cleaning their equipment, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0849)
  - Men who died at the Moose Hall fire in 1951, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0850)
  - Men who died at the Moose Hall fire in 1951, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0851)
  - Dean A.L. Stone when he was a member of Missoula Fire Department, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0852)
  - Dean A.L. Stone when he was a member of Missoula Fire Department, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0853)
  - Chiefs of fire department, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0854)
  - Old and new fire chiefs, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0855)
  - Fire engine at fire in back of Vince Bakke Tires, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0856)
  - Young girl sitting on fender of new fire engine, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0857)
  - Young girl sitting on fender of new fire engine, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0858)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station drive, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0859)
  - Arrival of new fire engine, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0860)
  - Pine Street, paving new fire station drive, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0861)
  - Pushing fire engine out of the fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0862)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0863)
  - Men who died at the Moose Hall fire in 1951, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0864)
  - Alarm system in the new fire house on Pine Street, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0865)
  - Fire engines parked in their fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0866)
  - Fire staff in front of the fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0867)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0868)
  - Fire engines out on show, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 2, Photo number 90-0869)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0870)
  - Arrival of new fire engine at railyard, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0871)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0872)
  - Pine Street, construction work on new fire station, Missoula, Montana, 1954 (Box 2, Photo number 90-0873)
  - Portrait of N.C. Peterson, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0874)
  - Arrival of new fire engine at railyard, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0875)
  - Arrival of new fire engine at railyard, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0876)
  - Arrival of new fire engine at railyard, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0877)
  - Arrival of new fire engine at railyard, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0878)
  - Testing fire engine #2 at McCormick Park, Missoula, Montana, September 29, 1954 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0879)
  - Three firemen, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0880)
  - Fire engines on site at Missoula Laundry during a fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0881)
  - Fire engines on site at Missoula Laundry during a fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0882)
  - Fire engines on site at Missoula Laundry during a fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0883)
  - Fire engines on site at Missoula Laundry during a fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0884)
  - House fire, 1st Street South, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0885)
  - Hotel Florence fire of 1913, Missoula, Montana (Box 3, Photo number 90-0886)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0887)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0888)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0889)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0890)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0891)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0892)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0893)
  - Fire engines at Yandt's/Gambles/Shapard fires, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0894)
  - Dousing the Hammond Building blaze, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0895)
  - Firefighters battle the Hammond building blaze, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0896)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0897)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0898)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0899)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0900)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0901)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0902)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0903)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins AvenuEast Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0904)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0905)
  - Fighting Pallas Candy Company fire on Higgins Avenue, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0906)
  - Mount Sentinel blaze seen from the Clark Fork River, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0907)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0908)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0909)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0910)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0911)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0912)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0913)
  - Loyola High School fire, Missoula, Montana, 1960 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0914)
  - Shapard Hotel Fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0915)
  - Shapard Hotel Fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0916)
  - Schematic drawing for an AM/FM 2 band transistor, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0917)
  - Schematic drawing for an AM/FM 2 band transistor, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0918)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0919)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0920)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0921)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0922)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0923)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0924)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0925)
  - Johnson Flying Service, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0926)
  - Aerial view of the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0927)
  - Aerial view of the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0928)
  - Aerial view of the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0929)
  - Setting up fire hose for the Yandt's Fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0930)
  - Firemen look on at the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0931)
  - Ice forming on the side of a building during fire fight, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0932)
  - Firemen douse an unidentified fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0933)
  - Things salvaged from an unidentified fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0934)
  - Administering first-aid to injured people at a fire, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0935)
  - Ice forming on the side of a building during fire fight, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0936)
  - Firemen battle the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0937)
  - Ice forming on the side of a building during fire fight, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0938)
  - Ice forming on the side of a building during fire fight, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0939)
  - Shapard Hotel Fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0940)
  - Wetting down a fire with a hose, Missoula, Montana, undated (Box 3, Photo number 90-0941)
  - Ice forming on Yandt's from during fire fight, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0942)
  - Firemen battle the Yandt's fire, Missoula, Montana, January 23, 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0943)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0944)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0945)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0946)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0947)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0948)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0949)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0950)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0951)
  - View of J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0952)
  - Missoula County Fairgrounds fire, Missoula, Montana, 1940 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0953)
  - Missoula County Fairgrounds fire, Missoula, Montana, 1940 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0954)
  - Missoula County Fairgrounds fire, Missoula, Montana, 1940 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0955)
  - Missoula County Fairgrounds fire, Missoula, Montana, 1940 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0956)
  - J.C. Penney fire, Missoula, Montana, circa 1955 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0957)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0958)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0959)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0960)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0961)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0962)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0963)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0964)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0965)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire on Ryman and Main Streets, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0966)
  - Ormesher Grocery fire on Ryman and Main Streets, Missoula, Montana, December 1952 (Box 3, Photo number 90-0967)